<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://xiangbei11.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://xiangbei11.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2025-04-29T17:04:22+00:00</updated><id>https://xiangbei11.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Xiangbei Liu</title><subtitle>A simple, whitespace theme for academics. Based on [*folio](https://github.com/bogoli/-folio) design. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">How Alpha Shapes the Dirichlet Distribution?</title><link href="https://xiangbei11.github.io/blog/2025/how-alpha-shapes-dirichlet-distribution/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How Alpha Shapes the Dirichlet Distribution?"/><published>2025-04-29T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-29T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://xiangbei11.github.io/blog/2025/how-alpha-shapes-dirichlet-distribution</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://xiangbei11.github.io/blog/2025/how-alpha-shapes-dirichlet-distribution/"><![CDATA[<p>In Python, sampling from a Dirichlet distribution looks deceptively simple:</p> <div class="language-python highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code><span class="n">np</span><span class="p">.</span><span class="n">random</span><span class="p">.</span><span class="nf">dirichlet</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="n">alpha</span><span class="p">,</span> <span class="n">size</span><span class="p">)</span>
</code></pre></div></div> <p>At first, I treated it just like another random generator — specify an <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">alpha</code>, draw some probability vectors, and move on. But as I used it more, I realized that <strong>alpha</strong> is not just a parameter. It fundamentally changes how the samples behave — shifting the Dirichlet distribution from sparsity to uniformity, from unpredictable peaks to smooth, balanced vectors.</p> <p>This blog is not about coding tricks. It’s about understanding what alpha really does, how it mathematically shapes randomness, and how even a small change in alpha leads to dramatically different outcomes.</p> <hr/> <h3 id="introduction-to-the-dirichlet-distribution"><strong>Introduction to the Dirichlet Distribution</strong></h3> <p>The Dirichlet distribution models <strong>probability vectors</strong> — lists of non-negative numbers that sum to 1. Formally, if:</p> <p>[ \mathbf{p} = (p_1, p_2, \dots, p_K) ]</p> <p>then ( \mathbf{p} ) is drawn from a Dirichlet distribution with parameter vector ( \boldsymbol{\alpha} = (\alpha_1, \alpha_2, \dots, \alpha_K) ) as:</p> <p>[ \mathbf{p} \sim \text{Dirichlet}(\boldsymbol{\alpha}) ]</p> <p>Each ( \alpha_k ) influences the corresponding component ( p_k ), controlling how large or small it tends to be across different samples.</p> <p>When I first used the Dirichlet function, I focused mainly on generating random compositions. But once I started varying alpha and observing the output, deeper patterns became clear.</p> <h3 id="the-role-of-alpha"><strong>The Role of Alpha</strong></h3> <p>When all ( \alpha_k ) are set to the same value (for example, ( \alpha = 1 ) for each component), the behavior of the Dirichlet distribution depends strongly on the size of alpha:</p> <ul> <li><strong>When ( \alpha &lt; 1 )</strong>: Samples tend to be <strong>sparse</strong>. Most of the probability mass concentrates in a few categories.</li> <li><strong>When ( \alpha = 1 )</strong>: Samples are <strong>uniform</strong> over the simplex — any combination is equally likely.</li> <li><strong>When ( \alpha &gt; 1 )</strong>: Samples become <strong>dense</strong> and <strong>balanced</strong>, with values clustering around equal proportions.</li> </ul> <p>Through experimentation, I noticed that when alpha was very small, a few elements dominated, while others were nearly zero. As alpha increased, samples became smoother, and no single element stood out sharply.</p> <h3 id="mathematical-properties"><strong>Mathematical Properties</strong></h3> <p>The <strong>expected value</strong> for each component ( p_k ) is:</p> <p>[ \mathbb{E}[p_k] = \frac{\alpha_k}{\sum_{i=1}^K \alpha_i} ]</p> <p>If all components have the same alpha, each expected probability is simply ( \frac{1}{K} ).</p> <p>More importantly, the <strong>variance</strong> of each ( p_k ) tells how much each component can fluctuate:</p> <p>[ \text{Var}[p_k] = \frac{\alpha_k(\alpha_0 - \alpha_k)}{\alpha_0^2 (\alpha_0 + 1)} \quad \text{where} \quad \alpha_0 = \sum_{i=1}^K \alpha_i ]</p> <p>When all ( \alpha_k ) are equal, this simplifies to:</p> <p>[ \text{Var}[p_k] \propto \frac{1}{\alpha (K\alpha + 1)} ]</p> <p>From this equation, the trend is clear: as ( \alpha ) increases, the variance decreases. Samples cluster closer to the expected uniform distribution. When ( \alpha ) is small, variance is large, and extreme values are much more likely.</p> <p>This mathematical behavior aligned exactly with what I observed in my Python simulations.</p> <h3 id="why-alpha--1-matters"><strong>Why Alpha = 1 Matters</strong></h3> <p>During my tests, I noticed that alpha = 1 seemed like a turning point. When alpha was less than 1, samples were sparse and uneven. When alpha was greater than 1, samples became more uniform and balanced.</p> <p>Mathematically, alpha = 1 corresponds to a <strong>uniform</strong> distribution over the probability simplex. No particular configuration is favored — every combination of probabilities is equally likely. This makes alpha = 1 a meaningful boundary between randomness dominated by few categories and randomness evenly spread across all categories.</p> <hr/> <h3 id="practical-implications"><strong>Practical Implications</strong></h3> <p>This behavior has real-world consequences. In machine learning, for example, using small alpha values in topic models or clustering algorithms tends to produce “hard” assignments — most weight is assigned to a few topics or clusters. Larger alpha values lead to “softer” assignments, where each sample belongs to multiple groups more evenly.</p> <p>In simulation experiments, adjusting alpha allowed me to control how diverse or focused the generated samples were. It wasn’t just about generating numbers — it was about tuning how much variation I wanted to model.</p> <h2 id="lessons-learned">Lessons Learned</h2> <p>What started as a simple Python function turned into a deeper exploration of how one parameter can control the shape of randomness itself. Understanding ( \alpha ) isn’t just about getting the math right. It’s about seeing how small changes in our assumptions ripple into the patterns we create.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[A deep dive into how the alpha parameter in the Dirichlet distribution controls the balance between sparsity and uniformity, blending hands-on experimentation with clear mathematical insights.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Does Stress Cause Strain — or the Other Way Around?</title><link href="https://xiangbei11.github.io/blog/2025/stress_strain/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Does Stress Cause Strain — or the Other Way Around?"/><published>2025-04-14T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-14T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://xiangbei11.github.io/blog/2025/stress_strain</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://xiangbei11.github.io/blog/2025/stress_strain/"><![CDATA[<p>In mechanics, the relationship between <strong>stress</strong> and <strong>strain</strong> is fundamental — but understanding <em>which causes which</em> is more nuanced and requires careful consideration.</p> <p>The standard view is that <strong>stress causes strain</strong>. Apply a force to a material (which creates <strong>stress</strong> — force per unit area), and the material deforms (which produces <strong>strain</strong> — deformation per unit length). This relationship is formalized by <strong>Hooke’s Law</strong> for linear elastic materials:</p> \[\epsilon = \frac{\sigma}{E}\] <p>Here, \(\epsilon\) is strain, \(\sigma\) is stress, and \(E\) is Young’s modulus — a material constant that quantifies stiffness. This equation treats stress as the input and strain as the output.</p> <p>However, in practical applications — especially in lab settings or engineering design — this relationship often seems reversed. We might <strong>impose a known strain</strong> by stretching or compressing a material by a fixed amount, and then measure the resulting stress. In this context, strain appears to come first, and stress becomes the system’s response.</p> <p>So, which one actually causes the other?</p> <h3 id="causality-depends-on-the-perspective"><strong>Causality Depends on the Perspective</strong></h3> <p><strong>Physically</strong>, external forces — such as loads, pressures, or constraints — generate internal stress within a material. The material then responds to that stress by deforming. In this framework, stress is the cause, and strain is the effect. This view aligns with how materials behave in the natural world.</p> <p><strong>Experimentally</strong>, however, the setup is often reversed. We control how much we stretch or compress a material (strain) and then observe how much resistance (stress) it produces. This doesn’t contradict the physical model — it simply shifts the practical focus to what’s being controlled versus what’s being measured.</p> <p><strong>Mathematically</strong>, the stress-strain relationship is linear (at least in the elastic range), so either stress or strain can be treated as the input, depending on the situation. The equation works in both directions.</p> <hr/> <h3 id="but-there-are-exceptions"><strong>But There Are Exceptions</strong></h3> <p>In many real-world cases, <strong>strain is the starting point</strong>, and the material reacts with internal stress.</p> <p>Take <strong>thermal expansion</strong> as an example: heating a material causes it to expand — that’s strain. If the material is free to expand, no stress develops. However, if it’s constrained, the expansion is resisted, and <strong>stress arises as a response to the imposed strain</strong>.</p> <p>A similar concept applies in <strong>shrink-fit assemblies</strong>, where a component is intentionally strained to fit tightly inside another. The strain is applied during assembly, and the resulting stress locks the parts together.</p> <p>In <strong>plastic deformation</strong>, once a material yields, it undergoes permanent strain even if the applied stress doesn’t increase. After unloading, residual strain remains — and in some cases, internal stress can also persist.</p> <p>These examples show that strain can sometimes be directly imposed, with the material’s internal stress developing as a response. In these cases, <strong>stress is not the original cause</strong>; rather, it’s the system’s reaction to a constraint or deformation.</p> <hr/> <h3 id="conclusion"><strong>Conclusion</strong></h3> <p>In classical mechanics, <strong>stress is typically considered the cause of strain</strong>, as external forces induce deformation. But in experimental settings and real-world applications, we also impose strain and measure the resulting stress. The key is context: <strong>what is being controlled</strong> and <strong>what is being observed</strong>.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post explores a question that popped into my head during a sunny afternoon at work]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What I Talk About When I Talk About Building Personal Website</title><link href="https://xiangbei11.github.io/blog/2025/website_build/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What I Talk About When I Talk About Building Personal Website"/><published>2025-04-03T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-04-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://xiangbei11.github.io/blog/2025/website_build</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://xiangbei11.github.io/blog/2025/website_build/"><![CDATA[<p>This post serves as a <strong>summary</strong> and <strong>guide</strong> based on my experience building a personal website using the <a href="https://github.com/alshedivat/al-folio">al-folio</a> Jekyll theme, hosted on GitHub Pages. It includes key setup steps, useful tips, and things I learned during the process.</p> <hr/> <h2 id="repository-structure-main-vs-gh-pages">Repository Structure: <strong>Main</strong> vs <strong>gh-pages</strong></h2> <p>Your GitHub repository will typically have two branches:</p> <ol> <li><strong>main</strong>: This is where you develop and manage your website’s source code (content, layouts, configurations, etc.).</li> <li><strong>gh-pages</strong>: This is where the <strong>static</strong> version of your site gets deployed after building it with Jekyll. GitHub serves this branch as the live site.</li> </ol> <h3 id="how-it-works">How It Works:</h3> <p>If you’re using <strong>GitHub Actions</strong> or any build script, the process is as follows:</p> <ul> <li><strong>Main</strong>: You work on the site by editing markdown files, configurations, and layouts.</li> <li><strong>gh-pages</strong>: Once you push changes to <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">main</code>, GitHub will rebuild the site and serve the static files in the <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">gh-pages</code> branch.</li> </ul> <p><strong>In short</strong>:</p> <ul> <li><code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">main</code>: Where you edit and develop.</li> <li><code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">gh-pages</code>: What the world sees when visiting your site.</li> </ul> <h3 id="to-confirm-automatic-deployment">To Confirm Automatic Deployment:</h3> <ol> <li>Check if you have GitHub Actions set up: Look for <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">.github/workflows</code> folder in your repo.</li> <li>If you see files like <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">deploy.yml</code> or <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">pages.yml</code>, the deployment is set up to automatically build and deploy to <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">gh-pages</code> when changes are pushed to <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">main</code>.</li> </ol> <hr/> <h2 id="reducing-menu-options">Reducing Menu Options</h2> <p>If you want to hide certain pages from the navigation bar, you can use the <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">nav: false</code> flag in the <strong>front matter</strong> of each page file (e.g., <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">cv.md</code>, <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">projects.md</code>).</p> <p>Example:</p> <div class="language-yaml highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code><span class="na">nav</span><span class="pi">:</span> <span class="kc">false</span>
</code></pre></div></div> <p>This will <strong>exclude the page from the navbar</strong>, even if it exists in the <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">_pages/</code> directory.</p> <p>You can also <strong>adjust the order</strong> of pages by using <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">nav_order</code>:</p> <div class="language-yaml highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code><span class="na">nav_order</span><span class="pi">:</span> <span class="m">1.5</span>  <span class="c1"># This will place the page between 1 and 2 in the navigation menu</span>
</code></pre></div></div> <p><strong>Note</strong>: If you set <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">nav: false</code>, the <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">nav_order</code> value will be ignored since the page won’t be in the navigation menu.</p> <hr/> <h2 id="highlighting-your-name-in-publications">Highlighting Your Name in Publications</h2> <p>To bold your name in publications (for example, in <strong>BibTeX</strong>), you can use the <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">highlight_author</code> field in <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">_config.yml</code>.</p> <p>Steps:</p> <ol> <li>Open <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">_config.yml</code>.</li> <li>Add your name like this:</li> </ol> <div class="language-yaml highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code><span class="na">scholar</span><span class="pi">:</span>
  <span class="na">last_name</span><span class="pi">:</span> <span class="pi">[</span><span class="nv">Liu</span><span class="pi">]</span>
  <span class="na">first_name</span><span class="pi">:</span> <span class="pi">[</span><span class="nv">Xiangbei</span><span class="pi">,</span> <span class="nv">X.</span><span class="pi">]</span>
</code></pre></div></div> <p>This will automatically <strong>bold your name</strong> in the publication section whenever it matches your name in the BibTeX <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">author</code> field.</p> <hr/> <h2 id="adding-social-media-links">Adding Social Media Links</h2> <p>To display social media links (e.g., LinkedIn, GitHub) in your website:</p> <ol> <li>Edit <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">_data/socials.yml</code>.</li> <li>Use the <strong>social network name</strong> and <strong>URL</strong>:</li> </ol> <div class="language-yaml highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code><span class="na">linkedin</span><span class="pi">:</span>
  <span class="na">url</span><span class="pi">:</span> <span class="s">https://www.linkedin.com/in/xiangbei-liu-208a70207</span>
<span class="na">github</span><span class="pi">:</span>
  <span class="na">url</span><span class="pi">:</span> <span class="s">https://github.com/xiangbei11</span>
</code></pre></div></div> <p>You can use the <strong>username</strong> directly instead of the full URL in most cases.</p> <hr/> <h2 id="ssh-key">SSH key</h2> <h3 id="setting-up-ssh-for-github">Setting Up SSH for GitHub</h3> <p>To securely push code to GitHub using SSH, follow these steps:</p> <ol> <li><strong>Generate an SSH key</strong>:</li> </ol> <div class="language-bash highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code>ssh-keygen <span class="nt">-t</span> ed25519 <span class="nt">-C</span> <span class="s2">"xiangbei.liu.th@dartmouth.edu"</span>
</code></pre></div></div> <ol> <li><strong>Copy your public key</strong>:</li> </ol> <div class="language-bash highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code><span class="nb">cat</span> ~/.ssh/id_ed25519.pub
</code></pre></div></div> <ol> <li><strong>Add the key to GitHub</strong>: <ul> <li>Go to <strong>GitHub → Settings → SSH and GPG Keys</strong>.</li> <li>Click <strong>New SSH Key</strong>, paste your public key, and save.</li> </ul> </li> <li><strong>Update your Git remote to use SSH</strong>:</li> </ol> <div class="language-bash highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code>git remote set-url origin git@github.com:xiangbei11/xiangbei11.github.io.git
</code></pre></div></div> <ol> <li><strong>Test the connection</strong>:</li> </ol> <div class="language-bash highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code>ssh <span class="nt">-T</span> git@github.com
</code></pre></div></div> <p>If everything is set up, you should see:</p> <div class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code>Hi xiangbei11! You've successfully authenticated...
</code></pre></div></div> <p>Now, you’re ready to <strong>push changes</strong>:</p> <div class="language-bash highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code>git push origin main
</code></pre></div></div> <h3 id="fixing-host-key-warnings-for-ssh">Fixing “Host Key” Warnings for SSH</h3> <p>If you see a warning about “Host key verification failed” when connecting to GitHub via SSH, it’s most likely due to a change in the SSH key. To fix it:</p> <ol> <li>Remove the old key:</li> </ol> <div class="language-bash highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code>ssh-keygen <span class="nt">-R</span> github.com
</code></pre></div></div> <ol> <li>Reconnect to GitHub:</li> </ol> <div class="language-bash highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code>ssh <span class="nt">-T</span> git@github.com
</code></pre></div></div> <p>Type <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">yes</code> when prompted, and the connection will be reset.</p> <hr/> <h2 id="working-with-font-sizes-and-new-lines-in-_configyml">Working with Font Sizes and New Lines in <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">_config.yml</code></h2> <ul> <li><strong>Multiline strings in YAML</strong>: The <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">&gt;</code> symbol allows you to format multiline strings, like the <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">blog_description</code>.</li> </ul> <div class="language-yaml highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code><span class="na">blog_description</span><span class="pi">:</span> <span class="pi">&gt;</span>
  <span class="s">&lt;em&gt;“When you come out of the storm, you won't be the same person...”&lt;/em&gt; — Haruki Murakami</span>
  <span class="s">This blog is my place to collect and make sense of what I’m learning...</span>
</code></pre></div></div> <ul> <li><strong>New Paragraphs</strong>: Use <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">&lt;p&gt;</code> tags for new paragraphs. To force a line break within the same paragraph, use <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">&lt;br&gt;</code>.</li> </ul> <hr/> <h2 id="understanding-rem-in-css">Understanding <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">rem</code> in CSS</h2> <ul> <li><code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">rem</code> stands for <strong>root em</strong>. It’s a relative unit based on the <strong>root</strong> font size (usually 16px by default).</li> </ul> <p>Example:</p> <ul> <li><code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">1rem = 16px</code></li> <li><code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">0.9rem = 14.4px</code></li> </ul> <p><code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">rem</code> makes it easier to scale font sizes across your site.</p> <hr/> <h2 id="changing-the-default-font-size-of-the-blog-page">Changing the Default Font Size of the Blog Page</h2> <p>To modify the default font size of the blog page, you’ll need to:</p> <ol> <li>Locate the theme’s CSS file (typically <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">assets/css/main.scss</code>).</li> <li>Override the font size for the blog page:</li> </ol> <div class="language-scss highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code><span class="nc">.post-content</span> <span class="p">{</span>
  <span class="nl">font-size</span><span class="p">:</span> <span class="m">0</span><span class="mi">.9rem</span><span class="p">;</span>  <span class="cm">/* Or any size you prefer */</span>
<span class="p">}</span>
</code></pre></div></div> <p>This will reduce the font size for the content of the blog.</p> <hr/> <h2 id="handling-external-blog-posts">Handling External Blog Posts</h2> <p>External blog posts are often included in your <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">_config.yml</code> under <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">external_sources</code>. To remove them:</p> <ol> <li>Open <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">_config.yml</code>.</li> <li>Comment out or delete the following block:</li> </ol> <div class="language-yaml highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code><span class="na">external_sources</span><span class="pi">:</span>
  <span class="pi">-</span> <span class="na">name</span><span class="pi">:</span> <span class="s">medium.com</span>
    <span class="na">rss_url</span><span class="pi">:</span> <span class="s">https://medium.com/@al-folio/feed</span>
  <span class="pi">-</span> <span class="na">name</span><span class="pi">:</span> <span class="s">Google Blog</span>
    <span class="na">posts</span><span class="pi">:</span>
      <span class="pi">-</span> <span class="na">url</span><span class="pi">:</span> <span class="s">https://blog.google/technology/ai/google-gemini-update-flash-ai-assistant-io-2024/</span>
        <span class="na">published_date</span><span class="pi">:</span> <span class="s">2024-05-14</span>
</code></pre></div></div> <p>This will stop these external posts from showing up on your blog.</p> <hr/> <h2 id="table-of-contents-toc-configuration">Table of Contents (TOC) Configuration</h2> <p>The <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">toc:</code> option in the front matter is used to generate a Table of Contents for the post:</p> <ul> <li><strong><code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">beginning: true</code></strong>: Places the TOC at the start of the post.</li> <li><strong><code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">end: true</code></strong>: Places the TOC at the end of the post.</li> <li><strong><code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">sidebar: true</code></strong>: Moves the TOC to the sidebar.</li> </ul> <p>Example:</p> <div class="language-yaml highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code><span class="na">toc</span><span class="pi">:</span>
  <span class="na">beginning</span><span class="pi">:</span> <span class="kc">true</span>
  <span class="na">max_level</span><span class="pi">:</span> <span class="m">2</span>
</code></pre></div></div> <p>This will place the TOC at the beginning and include only the first two levels of headings.</p> <hr/> <h2 id="todo">TODO</h2> <ul> <li>Submit the site to Google Search Console</li> <li>Change # of more authors to “et al.”</li> <li>Change the theme color</li> </ul> <hr/> <p>This guide captures the how-to steps that helped me set up and refine my site. If you’re building yours with al-folio, I hope this saves you time and effort!</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[A practical guide and reflection on building a personal academic website using al-folio]]></summary></entry></feed>